Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
5583/3
Kheel Center
86.3 linear ft.
Records, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Publications, manuals, policies, and plans issued by a large sample of Fortune 500 corporations and by a variety of organizations, such as professional and trade associations, government agencies, and educational and cultural organizations. The materials issued by corporations include company histories, employee newsletters, employee benefit plans, personnel practice manuals, performance appraisal forms, affirmative action policies, training brochures, job descriptions, and career development programs as well as national trade association documents and recruitment material.
Several economic activities(sectors) are represented in the collection, such as manufacturing, transportation, mining, banking, insurance, utilities, trade, and services. Corporations whose pamphlets are held in the collection include AT&T, Bethlehem Steel, Bell Telephone System, Firestone Tire & Rubber, Ford Motor Co., General Electric, General Foods, General Mills, General Motors, Goodyear Tire & Rubber, Heinz, International Harvester, Johnson & Johnson, Lockheed Aircraft Co., Maytag Co., Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., National Association of Manufacturers, Pennsylvania Railroad Co., Radio Corporation of America (RCA), Standard Oil, Tennessee Valley Authority, Union Carbide, and Westinghouse Electric among numerous other corporations.
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into four sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Boxes 82-87 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Pullman Company.; Pullman-Standard Car Manufacturing Company.; Purdue University.; Quaker Oats Company.; Radio Corporation of America. RCA Victor Division.; Railway Express Agency.; Ralston Purina Company.; Republic Aviation Corporation.; Republic Steel Corporation.; Research Council for Economic Security.; Research Institute of America, inc.; Resistoflex Corporation.; Revere Copper and Brass Incorporated.; Reynolds Metals Company.; Reynolds Metals Company. Consumer Products Division.; R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company.; Rheem Manufacturing Company.; Ritter-Conley Manufacturing.; Ritter Company.; Ritter-Pfaudler Corporation.; Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Company.; Rockbestos Product Corporation.; Royal McBee Corporation.; Rubber Manufacturers Association (U.S.); Rutgers University. Institute of Management and Labor Relations.; Rutgers University.; St. Regis Paper Company.; Samsonite Corporation.; San Diego Gas and Electric Company.; San Francisco Employers Council.; Sangamo Electric Company.; Sargent and Company (New Haven, Conn.); Scott Paper Company.; Sealed Power Corporation.; Sears, Roebuck and Company.; Shell Oil Company.; Sinclair Oil Corporation.; SKF Industries, inc.; Society for Advancement of Management.; Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals (U.S.); Socony Mobil Oil Company.; Socony-Vacuum Oil Company.; Solar Aircraft Company.; Southern California Edison Company.; Southern New England Telephone Company.; Southern Pacific Company.; Southern Regional Council.; Spencer Kellogg and Sons, Inc.; Sperry Gyroscope Company, inc.; Sperry Rand Corporation.; Standard Oil Company.; Standard Oil Company of California.; Standard Oil Company (Indiana); Standard Oil Company of New Jersey; Standard Oil Company (Ohio); Standard Oil Development Company.; State Farm Insurance Companies.; State Farm Mutual Automobile Insurance Company.; State Mutual Life Assurance Company (Worcester, Mass.); John B. Stetson Hat Company.; Stromberg-Carlson Telephone Manufacturing Co.; Studebaker Corporation.610:; Studebaker-Packard Corporation.; Sun Oil Company.; Supermarket Institute.; Swift & Company (Chicago, IL); Sylvania Electric Products, Inc.; Sylvania Electronics Systems.; Taylor Instrument Companies.; Tennessee Valley Authority.; Texaco, inc.; Texas Company.; Texas Instruments Incorporated.; Thatcher Glass Manufacturing Company.; Thompson Products, inc.; Thompson Ramo Wooldridge, inc.; Time, inc.; Time Share Corporation.; Timken Company.; Todd Shipyards Corporation.; Toledo Labor-Management-Citizens Committee.; Transportation Association of America.; Travelers Insurance Companies.; TRW Inc.; Tennessee Valley Authority.; Twentieth Century Fund.; Twin City Rapid Transit Company.; Union Bag-Camp Paper Corporation.; Union Carbide Corporation.; Union Electric Company of Missouri.; Union Labor Life Insurance Company.; Union Oil Company of California.; Union Pacific Railroad Company.; Uniroyal, inc.; United Aircraft Corporation.; United Airlines.; United Brands Company.; United Gas Corporation.; United Shoe Machinery Corporation.; U.S. Atomic Energy Commission.; United States. Bureau of Employment Security.; United States. Bureau of Federal Credit Unions.; United States. Bureau of Labor-Management Reports.; United States. Bureau of Labor Standards.; United States Civil Service Commission.; United States. Civil Aeronautics Administration; United States. Congress.; Job Corps (U.S.); U.S. Congress of Mayors.; United States. Department of Agriculture.; United States. Department of Commerce.; United States. Department of Defense.; United States. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.; United States. Department of Labor.; United States. Department of State.; United States. Department of the Air Force.; United States. Department of the Army.; United States. Department of the Interior.; United States. Department of the Navy.; United States. Department of the Treasury.; United States. Federal Trade Commission.; United States.General Accounting Office.; United States. General Services Administration.; United States. Internal Revenue Service.; United States. Interstate Commerce Commission.; Library of Congress; United States. National Labor Board.; United States.Office of Economic Opportunity.; United States. Railroad Retirement Board.; United States Rubber Company.; United States. Securities and Exchange Commission.; United States. Small Business Administration.; United States. Social Security Administration.; United States. Social Security Board.; United States Steel Corporation.; United States.Veterans Administration.; Volunteers in Service to America.; University of San Francisco.; Upjohn Company.; W.E. Upjohn Institute for Employment Research.; Upjohn Institute for Community Research.; Workmen's Compensation Board of Vancouver (B.C.); Victor Adding Machine Co.; University of Washington.; Washington University (Saint Louis, Mo.); Wayne State University.; Weirton Steel Corporation.; Welch's; University of the West Indies; West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company.; Western Electric Company.; Western Michigan University; Western Railways.; Western Union Telegraph Company.; Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Company.; Weston Electrical Company.; Weyerhaeuser Timber Company.; George Wiedemann Brewing Company.; H.W. Wilson Company; Wisconsin Electric Power Company; University of Wisconsin.; Wyandotte Chemicals Corporation.; Xerox Corporation.; Yale Towne Manufacturing Company; Yale University; Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company.; Zenith Radio Corporation.
Subjects:
Adult education; Aeronautics; Agricultural industries; Aluminum industry and trade; Airlines; Aircraft industry; Agricultural machinery; Architectural metal-work; Automobile industry and trade; Arbitration, Industrial; Agricultural chemicals industry; Audio equipment industry; Bituminous materials industry; Building trades; Buildings -- Environmental engineering; Banks and banking; Breweries; Baked products industry; Business consultants; Clothing trade; Coal mines and mining; Chemical industry; Compressor industry; Clerks (Retail trade); Computer industry; Cereal products; Consumer protection; Container industry; Credit unions; Clay industries; Cement industries; Copper alloys; Dairy products industry; Detergent industry; Executives --Training of; Electric power transmission; Electronics industries; Food industry and trade; Frozen foods and industry; Footwear industry; Fruit trade; Farm produce --Marketing -- Government policy; Finance, Public; Glass container industry; Glass manufacture; Gas extraction; Grain trade; Grocery trade; Gasket industry; Human capital; Hydroelectric power plants; Life insurance.; Iron industry and trade; Property insurance.; Casualty insurance.; Instructional materials industry; Health insurance.; Investment banking; Infant formula industry; Knit good industry; Labor unions; Local transit; Luggage industry; Logging; Medical supplies industry; Medicaid; Motor vehicle industry; Metal trade; Meat industry and trade; Military vehicle industry; Medical instruments and apparatus industry; Management; Measuring instruments; Natural gas pipelines; Notions (Merchandise); Newspaper publishing; Navigation equipment industry; National security; Office management; Office equipment and supplies; Petroleum refineries; Photographic industry; Paper folding (Graphic design); Public utilities; Paper products industry; Political participation; Plastics industry and trade; Pharmaceutical industry; Paint industry and trade; Public administration; Public opinion polls; Paper bag industry; Retail trade; Rug and carpet industry; Railroads; Rubber industry and trade; Railroad equipment industry; Roller bearings; Security systems industry; Service industries; Shipment of goods; Sanitary supply industry; Soybean industry; Slaughtering and slaughter-houses; Telecommunication.; Transportation equipment industry.; Trucking industry.; Trucks -- Design and construction.; Textile industry.; Trade associations.; Tobacco industry.; Universities and colleges.; Vocational education.; Wood products.; Welding equipment industry.; Woolen goods industry.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this Collection:
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3 5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Boxes 82-87 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 23, Folder: 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Language: English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: United States Business Performance Abroad, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Box: 23, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1970; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Box: 23, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1974; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Box: 23, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1969; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Box: 23, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Years of Business, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Box: 23, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Grievance Procedure, 1969; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Box: 23, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Highlights of IBM History, 1969; Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Box: 23, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Corporate Responsibility, 1975; Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Box: 23, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Profile of IBM, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Box: 23, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Education Information Bulletins, 1970; Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Box: 23, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Box: 23, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Box: 23, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Box: 23, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Careers and Opportunities, 1974; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Box: 23, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: IBM Opportunities For College Graduates, 1972; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Box: 23, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: IBM Employees 1971 Stock Purchase Plan, 1974; Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Box: 23, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Handbook, Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Box: 23, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Lecture Programmes, 1955; Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Box: 23, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Labor and Labor Relations, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Box: 23, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Safety Inspections, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Box: 23, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Realities and Opportunities In The Development of Jobs, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Box: 23, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: History Of Collective Bargaining In The Steel Industry, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Box: 23, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Manpower- Today's Frontier, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 24)
    Author: Frank H. Cassell
    Format: Publication
- Box: 23, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Businessman's Challenge In The Metropolis, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Box: 23, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Corporate Manpower Planning, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Box: 23, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Advances Management Program, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Box: 23, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Selection and Development of Managers, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Box: 23, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The Steel Import Situation, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 29)
    Author: Joseph L. Block
- Box: 23, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Steel Industry Outlook, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Box: 23, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Supply of Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Box: 23, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: College Graduates, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Box: 23, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Box: 23, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Chart, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Box: 23, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Box: 23, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Standards, 1957; Publication (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Box: 23, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relation Organization and Activities, 1958; Publication (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Box: 23, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Policy Manual, 1958; Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Box: 23, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Policies, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Box: 23, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1955; Publication (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Box: 23, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Box: 23, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Box: 23, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Box: 23, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Box: 23, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Ideas For Improvement, 1972; Publication (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Box: 23, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Handbook, Publication (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Box: 23, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: College Graduates, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 47)
    Author: William H. Lowe
- Box: 23, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Box: 23, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 49)
- Box: 23, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1974; Publication (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Box: 23, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Meeting Report, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Box: 23, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Disability Pensions, 1955; Publication (Box 23, Folder 52)
- Box: 23, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1953; Publication (Box 23, Folder 53)
- Box: 23, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 54)
    Author: William G. Caples
- Box: 23, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Business Topics, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 55)
- Box: 23, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Introduction of New Employees, Publication (Box 23, Folder 56)
- Box: 23, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Stock Ownership, 1953; Publication (Box 23, Folder 57)
- Box: 23, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Pensions, 1950; Publication (Box 23, Folder 58)
- Box: 23, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Management, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 59)
- Box: 23, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1954; Publication (Box 23, Folder 60)
- Box: 23, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1954; Publication (Box 23, Folder 61)
- Box: 23, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1953; Publication (Box 23, Folder 62)
- Box: 23, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Training Programs, 1953; Publication (Box 23, Folder 63)
- Box: 23, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Economics, 1951; Publication (Box 23, Folder 64)
- Box: 23, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: These Are The Facts, Mr. President, 1952; Publication (Box 23, Folder 65)
- Box: 23, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Communication In Industry, 1957; Publication (Box 23, Folder 66)
- Box: 23, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Management Development Review, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 67)
- Box: 23, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 68)
- Box: 23, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Employee Magazine, 1958; Publication (Box 23, Folder 69)
- Box: 23, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Research, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 70)
- Box: 23, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Administration, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 71)
- Box: 23, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Employment of Relatives, 1952; Publication (Box 23, Folder 72)
- Box: 23, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Credit Union, 1954; Publication (Box 23, Folder 73)
- Box: 23, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Vacation Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 23, Folder 74)
- Box: 23, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 75)
- Box: 23, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Tuition Reimbursement Policy, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 76)
- Box: 23, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Stock Ownership, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 77)
- Box: 23, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Insurance Group Life, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 78)
- Box: 23, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1954; Publication (Box 23, Folder 79)
- Box: 23, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Military Leaves Of Absence, 1951; Publication (Box 23, Folder 80)
- Box: 23, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1958; Publication (Box 23, Folder 81)
- Box: 23, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: The Challenging Years For Personnel Planning, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 82)
- Box: 23, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Management Development and Organization Planning, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 83)
- Box: 23, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 84)
- Box: 23, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Information Bulletin, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 85)
- Box: 23, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: A Personal Message To The Consultant, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 86)
- Box: 23, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 23, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 87)
- Box: 23, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 88)
- Box: 23, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 23, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Communication, 1958; Publication (Box 23, Folder 89)
- Box: 23, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 23, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: 1959 Proposals, Publication (Box 23, Folder 90)
- Box: 23, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 23, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Training Program, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 91)
- Box: 23, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 23, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 92)
- Box: 23, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 23, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Personnel Training, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 93)
- Box: 23, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 23, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Policy, 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 94)
- Box: 23, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 23, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Stock Ownership, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 95)
- Box: 23, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 23, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Insurance, 1950; Publication (Box 23, Folder 96)
- Box: 23, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 23, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Is Steel A Good Provider?, 1950; Publication (Box 23, Folder 97)
- Box: 23, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 23, Folder 98)